

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

-3+ years of experience in software development, especially full stack development with Reactjs and Nextjs -Always curious and willing to learn new things about frontend and backend -Can work independently or with a team -Experience working on a large project.

PROFILE

-High responsibility









SKILLS

HTML, CSS, TAILWIND, MUI 8/10

JAVASCRIPT 9/10

REACTJS, NEXTJS 9/10

FIREBASE, CI/CD, CLOUD FUNCTION 9/10

GIT 8/10

DOCKER

5/10

EDUCATION

2010-2015 Water Resources University

Major: Information Technology Engineer

NGUYEN TUNG BACH FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

OBJECTIVE

- -Always try to improve my technical and soft skills to become a better version of myself
- -Apply best practices from different experiences into actual project operations to deliver the most professional and maintainable codes
- -Proactive at work

WORK EXPERIENCE

IT SUPPORT // 2016 - 2019

EFY Viet Nam Company

Guide customer to use product and fix problems when installing

FRESHER DEVELOPER // 2010 - 2011

HNC Company (Hợp Nhất Quốc Tế)

Frontend and backend development

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER // 2021 - 2024

ClassFunc Company

Frontend and backend development

PROJECTS

> XROID STUDIO // 2023 -

Customer: Japanese

Team size: 16

Position: Fullstack Developer

- -Implement API, data structures Develop UI base components and implement core features
- -Discuss and propose solutions for new features
- -Guide new member to understand the source code, the flow of logic...

Technology description:

- Programming language: Javascript, HTML/CSS
- Framework: Next.js, NodeJS/Express, TailwindCSS, MUI
- Database: Firebase, Cloud Function
- Tool: Webstorm, Git

SOCIALSTEP // 2022 - 2023

Customer: Japanese

Team size: 20

Position: Frontend Developer

- -Develop UI base components, reate reusable components
- -Implement specific features (campaign page, template message...)
- -Implement additional features by customer's request
- -Fix bug

Technology description:

Same as above project